<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>from prior to posterior</title>
    <description>Paulo Roberto de Oliveira Castro Blog</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 17:38:19 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 17:38:19 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Paulo, I am a undergrad student at Universidade de São Paulo, and I’m starting a blog. The main goal with this is to organize my ideas and present what I learn in the University (and on the internet) in a way that is as simple to understand as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you’ll probably notice is that I edit my posts a lot. This is because I always find details that I want to enhance, but also because I’m not a native english speaker (resulting in several typos and grammatical errors that I will try to correct).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main subjects I will talk in this blog are Machine Learning, Programming, Probability, Bayesian Inference, Information Theory, Statistical Physics, Neuroscience, Bioinformatics and Evolution. Notice that I still haven’t decided what major area I will specialize in the future, so I’ll simply explore these and extract as much as I can from each of them. As we progress, I’ll naturally find out my main interests and this will be reflected in this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, I’ll preserve my interests in things other than science and eventually talk about politics in my country, cinema, television or music as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my journey,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paulo Roberto de Oliveira Castro&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/08/17/Introduction/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/08/17/Introduction/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
